<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Lazy Bison - Expert Ruby on Rails Development for SMEs on Мой Блог</title><link>http://localhost:1313/</link><description>Recent content in Lazy Bison - Expert Ruby on Rails Development for SMEs on Мой Блог</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 19:25:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Logistics in Motion: Overcoming Challenges and Achieving Excellence</title><link>http://localhost:1313/cases/2023-12-06-logistics-in-motioncase/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 19:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/cases/2023-12-06-logistics-in-motioncase/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Automating Deployments with Kamal and GitHub Actions</title><link>http://localhost:1313/blogs/2023-12-06-automating-deployments-blog/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 17:18:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/blogs/2023-12-06-automating-deployments-blog/</guid><description>Introduction: Simplify Your Deployments Learn how to automate your web app deployments using Kamal and GitHub Actions. This comprehensive guide covers installation, setup, and includes a sample configuration for seamless deployments.
Detailed Guide to Installing Kamal For a more in-depth look at installation and configuration, check out this detailed post.
Easy Steps to Install Kamal Direct Installation: Execute bundle add kamal to add the gem to your Ruby project.
Compatibility Note: May not work with older Ruby on Rails versions.</description></item><item><title>Effortless Deployment of Web Applications with Kamal</title><link>http://localhost:1313/blogs/2023-12-06-effortless-deployment-blog/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 17:18:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/blogs/2023-12-06-effortless-deployment-blog/</guid><description>Introduction Navigating the intricacies of web application deployment can be a daunting task. Enter Kamal—a deployment tool designed to alleviate these complexities. In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll delve into the key features of Kamal and share insights from our own hands-on experience.
Key Advantages of Kamal Kamal brings a host of features to the table, making it a go-to solution for web application deployment:
Zero Downtime: Kamal ensures uninterrupted service during the deployment process.</description></item><item><title>Expense Elegance: The Art of Spending with Balancer</title><link>http://localhost:1313/cases/2023-12-06-expense-elegance-case/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 17:18:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/cases/2023-12-06-expense-elegance-case/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>